EWA SAMBERGER

CONTACT

571-241-3859

 \boxtimes

ewa.samberger1@gmail.com



https://ewasamberger.github.io/Resume/



Ewa Samberger



Springfield, MO

SKILLS



LANGUAGES



PROFILE

I am a driven and dedicated student pursuing a degree in Cyber-Risk Management at Drury University. My coursework has exposed me to management, coding, various operating systems, and the dynamic field of cybersecurity. I am a member of a successful cyber defense club and the captain of the women's tennis team. My goal is to continuously learn and grow while gaining valuable work experience.

EDUCATION

Drury University

2021-Present

Major: Cyber-Risk Management Minor: Computer Science

Certificate: Learn to Lead & Lead to Learn GPA(2023) 3.68

CERTIFICATES

Pre-Security Certificate(TryHackMe)

Collaborative Institutional Training Initiative(CITI PROGRAM)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Tennis Coach 2023-Present

I am responsible for coaching tennis groups of every age and level of advancement. Working as a tennis coach is helping me gain experience in leadership, teamwork, and communication.

Cyber Security Technician 2023-Present Drury University

I am a part of the IT department at Drury University, working with the university's cyber security systems and policies. I design, modify, and upgrade policies for Drury University. A big part of my job is modifying, labeling, and monitoring the university's switches and servers. I am familiar with GDPR, FERPA, and HIPAA regulations. My responsibilities include creating a cybersecurity plan under NIST regulations and reviewing existing plans. That includes risk assessment and incident response planning.